University of Connecticut, Commencement Committee Records 1998.0245
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Commencement Committee Records
undated, 1926-1985.
1998.0245
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
1.0 Linear feet
This is a collection of files pertaining to University Commencement Ceremonies beginning in 1929 through 1971, with some gaps.
University of Connecticut, Commencement Committee.
History
Unknown.
Scope and Content
This is a collection of files pertaining to University Commencement Ceremonies beginning in 1929 through 1971, with some gaps. The files seem to have originated from the Commencement Committee, and can contain programs, tickets, correspondence, instructions to staff and graduates, notes, and expenditures. In a few cases, minutes of meetings, and copies of the commencement address are included. Also included in the collection are files on the inaugurations of Presidents George A. Works (1929), Charles C. McCracken (1931), Albert N. Jorgensen (1936), Glenn W. Ferguson (1974), and John A. DiBiaggio (1979) which contain similar material.
Arrangement
Series I: Records ( undated, 1926-1985 )
Acquisition Information
The files appear to have originated from the Commencement Committee and were transferred to the University Archives prior to 1998.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Administrative Records.; Archives.; Commencement ceremonies—Connecticut.; Correspondence.; Universities.; University of Connecticut.; University of Connecticut—Commencement exercises.
- Series I: Records, undated, 1926-1985
  - Commencements
    - 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - 1927 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - 1928 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - 1929 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - 1930 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - 1931 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - 1932 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - 1934 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - 1935 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - 1936 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - 1937 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - 1939 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - 1944 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
    - 1946 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - 1947 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - 1948 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - 1949 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - 1950 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - 1952 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - 1953 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 23-24)
    - 1955 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
    - 1956 (Box 1:, Folder 26-27)
    - 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - 1958 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
    - 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
    - 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
    - 1961 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
    - 1962 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
    - 1963 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
    - 1964 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
    - 1965 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
    - 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
    - 1968 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
    - 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 39)
    - 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
    - 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 41)
  - Inaugurations
    - George A. Works, 1929 (Box 1:, Folder 42)
    - Charles C. McCracken, 1931 (Box 1:, Folder 43)
    - Albert N. Jorgensen, 1936 (Box 1:, Folder 44)
    - Glenn W. Ferguson, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
    - John A. DiBiaggio, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified, undated, 1974, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 47)